{
 "data": [
    {
      "question": "___ was running behind the cat.",
      "a": "Black and white dog",
      "b": "A black and a white dog",
      "c": "The black and a white dog",
      "d": "A black and white dog",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- A black and while dog= a dog whose spur has two colors: black and white",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "20",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "I paid ___ price for this camera.",
      "a": "a double",
      "b": "double a",
      "c": "double the",
      "d": "the double",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- We often say: double something, twice a week...: obmiss article",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "20",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "I have never seen ___.",
      "a": "so brave a boy",
      "b": "so a brave boy",
      "c": "a so brave boy",
      "d": "so brave boy",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- Structure: so brave a boy= a very brave boy",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "20",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jack is as ___ as his brother.",
      "a": "a tall man",
      "b": "tall man",
      "c": "tall a man",
      "d": "taller a man",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Structure: tall a man= a man who is as tall as",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "20",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "She was ___ girl that they all loved her.",
      "a": "a such nice",
      "b": "such a nice",
      "c": "such nice",
      "d": "such nice a",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- Structure\nSuch a + noun phrase: used to emphasize your description of something or someone",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "20",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "London Bridge over ___ is very famous.",
      "a": "Thames",
      "b": "a Thames",
      "c": "The Thames",
      "d": "one Thames",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Some places and countries, and all rivers and oceans, have the as part of their name",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "20",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is better to tell ___ than to tell a lie.",
      "a": "the truth",
      "b": "a truth",
      "c": "truths",
      "d": "truth",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- Structure: tell the truth",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "20",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Of the two this is ___.",
      "a": "very more useful",
      "b": "much more useful",
      "c": "the more useful",
      "d": "most useful",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- The: \t used to show that you are talking about a particular thing or person\nThis case, the speakers mention a specific thing which is more useful",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "20",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "My father was appointed ___ of the city last year.",
      "a": "mayor",
      "b": "a mayor",
      "c": "the mayor",
      "d": "one mayor",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- Position or title normally don't have article",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "20",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "___ Kennedy is still very much loved by many people in the world.",
      "a": "Late President",
      "b": "A late President",
      "c": "The late President",
      "d": "Late a President",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Normally, Position or title normally don't have \"the\" \nHowever, in this case, the is used to show that you are talking about a particular thing or person",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "20",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ] 
}